http://www.phionline.com/topic/privacypolicy

Progressive Hydraulics, Inc.
0
Loading Mini-cart...
0
Loading Mini-cart...
All Pneumatics
Air Prep (FRL's)
Vendor Managed Inventory
Parker Tracking System (PTS)
Hose Doctor®
Company
Who is PHI?
Privacy Policy
SECTION 1 – WHAT DO WE DO WITH YOUR INFORMATION?
When you purchase something from us, as part of the buying and selling process, we collect the personal information you give us such as your name, address and email address. When you browse our site, we also automatically receive your computer's internet protocol (IP) address in order to provide us with information that helps us learn about your browser and operating system. Email marketing (if applicable): with your permission, we may send you emails about us, new products and other updates.
SECTION 2 – CONSENT
How do you get my consent?
When you provide us with personal information to complete a transaction, place an order, arrange for a delivery or return a purchase, we imply that you consent to our collecting it and using it for that specific reason only. If we ask for your personal information for a secondary reason, like marketing, we will either ask you directly for your expressed consent, or provide you with an opportunity to say no.
How do I withdraw my consent?
If after you opt-in, you change your mind, you may withdraw your consent for us to contact you, for the continued collection, use or disclosure of your information, at anytime, by contacting us at help@phionline.com or mailing us at: Progressive Hydraulics, Inc., 350 North Midland Avenue, Saddle Brook, NJ 07663.
SECTION 3 – DISCLOSURE
We may disclose your personal information if we are required by law to do so or if you violate our Terms of Service.
SECTION 4 – THIRD-PARTY SERVICES
In general, the third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us. However, certain third-party service providers, such as payment gateways and other payment transaction processors, have their own privacy policies in respect to the information we are required to provide to them for your purchase-related transactions. For these providers, we recommend that you read their privacy policies so you can understand the manner in which your personal information will be handled by these providers. In particular, remember that certain providers may be located in or have facilities that are located at different jurisdiction than either you or us. So if you elect to proceed with a transaction that involves the services of a third-party service provider, then your information may become subject to the laws of the jurisdiction(s) in which that service provider or its facilities are located.  Once you leave our website or are redirected to a third-party website or application, you are no longer governed by this Privacy Policy or our website's Terms of Service.
SECTION 5 – SECURITY
To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems and who are required to keep the information confidential. You understand that Progressive Hydraulics, Inc. uses a third party vendor to accept forms of payment. You understand that the payment information provided is never received by Progressive Hydraulics, Inc. and therefore Progressive Hydraulics, Inc. is not responsible for the safeguarding of such information. After a transaction, your private payment information (credit card information, etc.) will not be stored on our server.
SECTION 6 – COOKIES
Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
SECTION 7 – CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time, so please review it frequently. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on the website.
QUESTIONS AND CONTACT INFORMATION
If you would like to access, correct, amend or delete any personal information we have about you, register a complaint, or simply want more information contact us at help@phionline.com or by mail at Progressive Hydraulics, Inc. 350 North Midland Avenue, Saddle Brook, NJ 07663.
Products & Services
Online Store
Hose Assemblies
Kitting Services
Vendor Managed Inventory
Parker Tracking System (PTS)
©2020 Progressive Hydraulics, Inc.
Terms & Conditions |
Privacy Policy
Updating...
